<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Centered Space, LLC – Counseling and Meditation</title>
    <link>https://bridgetdunnavantcscm.com/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Centered Space, LLC – Counseling and Meditation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 14:38:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bridgetdunnavantcscm.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Services Provided and Therapeutic Style</title>
      <link>https://bridgetdunnavantcscm.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 14:38:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bridgetdunnavantcscm.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>I offer both individual and couples counseling to adults of all ages. I also teach mindfulness meditation in combination with traditional therapy when desired.
I assist individuals with a variety of goals, concerns, and difficulties. In addition to ameliorating symptoms, decreasing emotional pain, and helping to solve problems, I believe therapy can facilitate significant personal growth and increased wellness. Although most individuals could foreseeably benefit from the counseling process from this viewpoint, common issues with which I work include anxiety, depression, relationship and family distress, loss- and other trauma- related reactions, decision-making, general life transitions, and other stressors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio and Credentials</title>
      <link>https://bridgetdunnavantcscm.com/page/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 13:16:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bridgetdunnavantcscm.com/page/bio/</guid>
      <description>I received a BA in Psychology, with a minor in Studio Art, from Transylvania University located in Lexington, KY, and a MS in Community Counseling from Austin Peay State University in Clarksville, TN. I then went on to earn a PhD in Counseling Psychology from The University of Memphis, where I acquired additional clinical training in process-experiential methods, and concentrations in qualitative inquiry and social justice. I interned at the University of Florida Counseling and Wellness Center and have since been working in private practice in Richmond, VA.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>